Shane O Halloran

Email: ohalloran.shane@gmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/shaneohalloranbis/ | Website: shaneohalloran.com

Profile

I completed my degree in Business Information Systems at University College Cork having achieved a First Class Honours. I am a hardworking, motivated and reliable person. I have gained strong communication, organisational and time-management skills from my previous work experiences including a six-month internship in New York.

Work Experience

Business Analyst: EviView Limited | Cork, Ireland

December 2020 - Present

- I am an SME of our application software. I have effectively hosted training sessions with large groups of endusers.
- Translate client business needs into software requirements used to create concise and fully understandable user stories and requirements documentation.
- Facilitate solution reviews and feedback sessions with clients to ensure alignment with expectations.
- · Create interactive software mockups using *Google DevTools* and product design web applications.

Web Production Intern: Northwell Health (Marketing and Communications) | New York, USAMarch 2019 - August 2019

- · Carried out updates to all Northwell Health websites using their Drupal Content Management System implementing my knowledge of *HTML*, *CSS*, and *JavaScript*.
- · Corresponded with requestors and project managers to create production schedules outlining expected completion dates for various projects.
- Collaborated with other members of the Digital Strategy team including web developers, UX designers and QA testers. Wrote retrieval and store *SQL* queries for the database of a dynamic web application.
- · Created training documentation to improve the onboarding process for future interns.

Retail Sales Assistant: CeX | Cork, Ireland

January 2017 - January 2019

- · Processed in-store and online transactions, handled customer queries and tested technology products.
- Trained in supervisory tasks including opening and closing the store, counting the shop safe, transferring stock and processing refunds.

Education

BSc Business Information Systems - *University College Cork, Ireland*

2016 - 2020

- · Achieved a 1.1 First Class Honours Degree.
- Received IIBA Academic Certificate in Business Analysis after completing courses related to IS Development Methods and Software Quality.
- · Studied modules related to User Interaction/Design, Programming, Accounting and Business Analysis.

Skills

Technical: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Java, Video Editing and Microsoft Suite.

Analytical: Strategic Thinking, Problem Solving and Data Analysis. **Personal:** Creative, Team Oriented and Excellent Communicator.